

NIMRA SHAHZADI

WEB DEVELEPER

Address

NAZAMABAD,STREET # 12

CONTACT

+111 333 000 666 222 333

yourmail@doman.com

linkedin.com/yourprofile

PRO SKILL

PHOTOSHOP

ILLUSTRATOR

COREL DRAW

PROFILE

Start with your current or most recent job. Follow it with the one before it, then the one before and so on. In each entry list: your position, the name of the company, and the dates worked. Under each job, put up to 5 bullet points. Start with your current or most recent job. Follow it with the one before it, then the one before and so on. In each entry list: your position, the name of the company, and the dates worked. Under each job, put up to 5 bullet points

EXPERIENCES

PRODUCT DESIGNER ABC CORPORATION

IN 2014-2015

Start with your current or most recent job. Follow it with the one before it, then the one before and so on. In each entry list: your position, the name of the company, and the dates worked.

USER INTERACTION DESIGNER BEAT IT LTD,USA

IN 2016-2017

Start with your current or most recent job. Follow it with the one before it, then the one before and so on. In each entry list: your position, the name of the company, and the dates worked.

3D MODEL ARTIST ABC CORPORATIONS

IN 2017-2018

Start with your current or most recent job. Follow it with the one before it, then the one before and so on. In each entry list: your position, the name of the company, and the dates worked.

EDUCATION

MASTER OF FINAL ART UNIVERSITY OF DHAKA

IN 2014-2015

Start with your current or most recent job. Follow it with the one before it, then the one before and so on. In each entry list: your position, the name of the company, and the dates worked.

BACHELOR OF FINAL ART UNIVERSITY OF DHAKA

IN 2014-2015

Start with your current or most recent job. Follow it with the one before it, then the one before and so on. In each entry list: your position, the name of the company, and the dates worked.

TRAININGS